Daolin Sheng



15900859362@163.com



86 15900859362



linkedin.com/in/daolin-sheng-296591110

Summary

My name is Daolin Sheng, Male, Bachelor degree, Software development engineer. I have been working in Shanghai, China before and more than 6 years of software development experience. Otherwise, I Obtained PMP and NPDP certificates. Now, I'm studying for a Master of Advanced Computer Science (AI) at the University of Leeds.

Experience



Unemployed

None

Jul 2020 - Present (4 months +)

Senior Software Engineer

ArcherMind Technology (Nanjing) Co., Ltd. Aug 2019 - Jul 2020 (1 year)

Senior Software Engineer

Shanghai Three Zero Guard Infromation Secturity Co., Ltd Mar 2016 - Jul 2019 (3 years 5 months)

System Engineer

Guangzhou Advanced Digital Technology Co.,Ltd May 2015 - Mar 2016 (11 months)

Java Software Engineer

Shanghai Yuantong Express (Logistics) Co Ltd Aug 2014 - Apr 2015 (9 months)

Education



Zhengzhou University

Associate's degree, Computer Software Technology/Technician 2010 - 2012

Nanyang Institute of Technology

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science and Technology 2012 - 2014

Licenses & Certifications

- 信息系统项目管理师 中华人民共和国工业和信息化部 17101310221
- Python for Data Science Coursera
 GE25BXRTMY8J
- Data Analysis with Python Coursera
 GPJKJ8XVLUQC
- Python for Applied Data Science Coursera
- Project Management Professional (PMP)® Project Management Institute Issued Sep 2017 Expires Sep 2023
- New Product Development Professional (NPDP) PDMA Product Development and Management Association
 Issued Oct 2018 Expires Nov 2021
 C30070

Skills

Java • Python (Programming Language) • MATLAB • SQL • Software Development • Project Management • Product Development